"Frozen Snowflake Cone"
It looks like this.
- Yes, Mom ... Laura has played a little with yours.
- Yes, mine is beaten.
Laura didn't like yours.
The ice cream melts quickly here in Portugal, so now we have to munch.
Oh, Laura absolutely wants to munch.
- It feels pretty small.
- Can she start?
Or, should we start?
- Doesn't it feel a little small?
- It feels very small!
- tiny ice cream.
- So, we drive.
Can I taste too?
It is blueberry ice cream.
Super good.
(Harry) nom, nom, nom.
Oh, Laura is not visible in the camera.
Maybe was just as good.
She doesn't have such a good table.
I like the taste, and I like the aftertaste, so this one was, etc., actually very good.
What points do you give from 1-5?
- I give a strong 3rd.
- (Joanna) oooh ...
- I give a 3rd.
- I also give a 3rd.
Oh...
- Top on a hot summer day!
- Aaah!
My hands!
- What?
What is it?
- It's so cold by hand.
Aaaah!
- I like this one.
- They have frozen together.
They can't move.
The sugar is starting to get up in the heads of them.
Yes, it goes so fast.
I also feel much nicer.
I was a little tired when we started recording.
Now, just, "ding-dong"!
Yes, really "ding-dong".
Or it depends ...
-♪ "pure frame ding-dong, came all the nicke doll with us!"
♪ - Nämen ... Not the one.
♪ "pure frame ding-dong!"
♪
Oh my God.
Not only are you forced to look at the Melodifestivalen over the years, you should also have to hear those odors to songs.
- Stop being so bitter.
- I'm so bitter.
Oh, it was like ... there was so much in this one.
Yes, you liked it.
- Almost like Arne's brine.
- huh?!
After all, it is not even like anything with brine.
- Arnes brine.
- What was it from?
What is that?
- I think it was a news last year from Sia or Triumf.
- Arnes ...
- Don't you remember when I kind of spit?
- Yes exactly.
Uncle Arne.
- Down here in Portugal, brine ice cream would never work.
- No.
GB has a brine chalk ... or, at least a licorice ice cream, as news in Sweden, but no Portuguese would buy it, ever!
- They don't eat licorice down here.
They don't eat candy ... - No.
They have a completely different culture around sweets.
- Zero?!
- "Scanner Eyes."
- He doesn't like chocolate ice cream.
- No.
There are second zero Harry today.
- Harry doesn't like "Salted Caramel".
- Aha.
I give 4 points.
What does Laura give?
- Five!
- Wooo!
- What is this?
- I spilled Calippo Lemon.
- You made the classic mistake and turned it.
- not "lemon" - "lime".
Calippo lime.
Not "lemon".
- "Don't do it."
Never turn a Calippo upside down.
- No.
We have a question of the day.
Alma, you are here, because it is for you.
Okay.
Yeah!
- Yes, I will!
- Yes, she will!
Pipito is included!
Yes, I will.
- Yes, you will?
- Yes!
- When should it be finished, then?
- I don't really know, but there will be one.
Keep an eye on Alma's channel.
"Solero Barrinha Manga"
It looks like this.
If you translate "Barrinha", it means "barbell" in Swedish.
- In Sweden, a new sandwich ice cream has come out.
- A new taste on sandwich.
Yes exactly.
This is Portugal's version on Sandwich.
- You have on the upper lip ... - No, a 4th only.
Not strong.
4 points?
I give this 0 points.
A really, really zero zero.
“Cornetto Rose”
It looks like this.
Like a rose.
This is not a news in Sweden this year.
It says it is "Raspberry Milkshake Flavor".
It is thus raspberry mile shake flavor.
Okay, are you prepared?
1, 2, 3!
- (Harry) Mmm.
- (shoulder) mm.